Laleh Saadatmand Moghadam

Email: Lalehsaadatmand@gmail.com Tell: 4696626820 US Citizen

 Passionate Student of Master of Applied Cognition& Neuroscience specialized in Human Computer Interaction (HCI) area. I am a UX/UI designer loving to improve life experience by my skills. I eagerly look forward to expanding my knowledge and skillset and finding new opportunities to grow. Each of my projects have provided growth by learning concepts and theories of UX/UI design, allowing me to establish myself within this competitive industry. I am detail oriented and enjoy working on products from ideation all the way to development.

Education

•	Student of Master of Applied Cognition Neuroscience	2023 - Present
	(Human Computer Interaction)	
•	Bachelor of Nursing (RN), Azad University, Iran	2004 - 2008

Certifications

•	Responsive Web Design in Adobe XD	2023
•	Create High-Fidelity Designs and Prototypes in Figma	2022
•	UX research and test early concepts certificate, Google certified	2021
•	UX design Process Empathize, Define, and Ideate Google certified	2021
•	Build Wireframes and low-Fidelity Prototypes, Google certified	2021
•	Foundation of User Experience (UX) design, Google certified	2021
•	Healthcare course in Educational Organization, Iran	2012

Achievement

• Successfully Completed UX/UI Design project-based program Feb 2021 – Aug 2021

Skills

- Proficient in prototyping tools such as Adobe XD, Figma, Sketch, InVision, etc.
- Detail oriented and have a keen eye for aesthetics.
- Excellent communication skills and can clearly articulate your ideas, designs, and suggestions.
- Strong teamwork capability
- Creative with thorough research skills
- Ability to derive core insights about user behavior and understanding

- A natural inclination towards user experience and excellent usability
- Knowledge of current and upcoming design trends with a high aptitude for learning
- Ability to translate user and developer input into solution.

Professional Experience

Sales associate at Dillard's, Plano, TX

5/2016 - 6/2021

- Assisted customers in the women's department to choose clothing style
- Processed transactions with different kinds of credit cards.
- Merchandised items.
- Managed customers' orders by phone and computer.

Sales associate at Walmart, Plano, TX

3/2015-5/2016

- Operated cash registers, processed transactions, and delivered customer service.
- Assisting customers find things they need.
- Merchandised items.

Sales associate at Macy's, Plano, TX

10/2014-3/2015

- Assisted customers find the appropriate stuff, they need.
- Merchandising items.

Surgical Nurse (RN)

Salamat Clinic, Qom, Iran

3/2009 - 12/2010

Salamat Clinic is a well-equipped with all up-to-date equipment composing of mandible surgery, gum surgery, orthodontic, dental implant, endodontic, periodontal and radiology departments with +80 surgeons, specialists, dentists, dental assistants, nurses, and radiology technologists.

- Performed quality Patient care.
- Arranged and set appointments.
- Interred insurance and billing information in the system by computer
- Prepared patients for procedures
- Maintained patient rooms and units and stocked necessary office and surgical supplies.
- Prepared the room, setting up surgical tools needed for sterile surgical procedures.
- Taken and recorded patient history
- Instructed and prepared patient for the procedure.
- Followed the clinical protocols.
- Kept patient records accurately and confidentially.